Today my grandpa becomes the President of the United States again.
Let's go.
How many hours did you sleep last night?
Four hours.
I'm cooked.
Kai's cooked.
Yeah, I like your hair straight like that.
That looks really nice.
I think so.
You're welcome, Kai.
Yeah, I like your hair like that too.
It looks really nice.
You're being sarcastic.
I don't like the way you said that.
I don't even think I put a brush through it.
By the way, your hair looks amazing, Riley.
Alright.
Alright, we just finished the
church ceremony and now we're heading to the capitol for him to get sworn in.
We're running a little behind time, but that's okay.
Are you excited?
I mean, yeah, now that like after like being in the church, like it made
it more like real, you know?
Like I don't think I've processed it and now I'm like starting to like process
it.
So it's a lot at once, but you know, very excited for the whole family.
So it's gonna be awesome.
Girl, I'm literally just tasting everything.
Emma, bro, you're still eating popcorn.
Like, last night you were eating popcorn in the video, then today in the morning
you're eating popcorn.
What?
Capital coming up, right in front.
Alright guys, we're at the capital right now.
Let's do this.
Of course you found a coffee
store in the capital.
Seriously.
Oh you got another cookie?
I was going to text you to bring me a chocolate chip cookie.
Please bring me a cookie.
It's like two hours until he gets more in.
We're going live.
Dad, do you want to say something to the vlog?
I want to say something.
I love this little smurf so much, and I'm so proud of her.
I jumped her yesterday to ask if she wanted to speak in front of like
25,000 people randomly live, and she absolutely crushed it like she always does, so I'm
very proud of her.
And even if at her age dads are not cool, I don't care.
I love her so much.
You're the best, Liza.
I love you, too.
Good job.
Thank you.
Hope you guys are having a good time watching.
And tonight we're dancing.
We are dancing.
I don't know that we've ever slow danced so this could be pretty interesting we've
never slow danced have you ever seen like an official one I don't think we
have I don't think we have so we're going to have two people with two
left feet so it's going to get it's going to get interesting Kai's going to
break out some of her break dancing moves it's going to be awesome she practices
a lot at home I was thinking about like the frat flick yeah she's please
don't do that one
what a chiller what a chiller what a chill guy what a chill guy alright
guys so now we're going to go down right now to watch I'm about to
get sworn in.
We'll see how much we can film.
Obviously it's very private right now.
So yeah, we gotta go.
We gotta go.
We'll see.
Gloria!
Guys, I think I have a new celebrity crush.
Uh-oh.
Is it me?
Nate Archibald from Gossip Girl.
You're so red.
Yeah.
I'm so tired.
I have not drank anything, like any water.
Sure have energy drinks and coffee.
And I'm exhausted.
It's been three hours last night.
Awesome.
Okay, guys.
I'm sorry to push.
That was a whole different level of cold.
I don't think I've ever felt that.
Just us ruining the audience.
That was lethal.
That was a vicious cold.
Is
this weekend taking it out of you yet?
I mean, it hasn't really been a lot.
Just like we haven't really, like, we've had things that run really late and then
we've got to wake up really early, so it's just not like a lot of
hours to sleep.
But, I mean, I think a golf tournament takes away more out of you than
this.
And now, I get to introduce my dear
friend and President of the United States, Donald J.
Trump.
Another thing is that we're not out of time.
Stay there.
I
thought
that was really cool but I'm upset about one thing.
What?
Your tele girl didn't get a shout out.
She's famous too right?
Yeah I was expecting a shout out.
I'm sorry Anna.
I'm sorry, next time, next time.
I have no clue what the plan is right now, so we'll figure that out.
I think we're going to go to the White House, and then we've got to
branch off and go and get ready for the ball tonight.
If you were to explain this week in a few words, how would you describe
it?
Experience of a lifetime.
A little crazy.
Memorable, for sure.
Those three words.
What is it like seeing your grandfather up there on the stage as the 47th
president of the United States?
To me, he's just like a normal grandpa.
So right now we're going to head back to the hotel to get ready for
the Starlight Ball where me and my dad are dancing.
Obviously, because this is coming out after the ball.
Now, you guys will know that, yes, I am dancing with my dad tonight.
I've never danced before.
I'm not a very good dancer.
I've never claimed to be a good dancer, and tonight's going to be interesting.
I've never ball danced or anything like that, so it's the first time we haven't
even practiced because we're running two hours behind the schedule.
But we are going to do it somehow, and we're going to be the best
dancers out there on that stage.
So cheers to that.
I'm really excited to wear my sherry hill dress tonight.
It has like silver kind of like sequins diamonds It's really cute and I can't
wait to wear it.
I told them I go.
This looks like my wedding dress No, I mean this is jaw dropping Oh my
god dropping this whole thing for eyes obviously have silver but just add more silver
sparkle Not really do any more Eye shadow.
There we go Thank you guys.
I appreciate it.
Of course.
Did you guys order another chocolate?
No I'm really really hungry.
Okay, go eat something.
There's no food.
What?
I said there's no food, that's why I ate the box!
i'm gonna look that way what's that over there
all right guys today i'm wearing sherry hill again thank you so much sherry hill
for sending me all these dresses they look beautiful and i cannot wait to show
this off to the whole world tonight when i'm dancing with my dad my favorite
part of this um dress is the corset part because it just makes it look
really flattering and i like it a lot but also i love like all the
diamonds and like shivery stuff.
I think it looks really, really nice on my skin tone.
So guys, now we're heading to the White House to see my grandpa and then
ride with him to the Liberty Bowl, where I will be dancing the cha-cha slide.
To the left.
Take one back now.
Really?
Everyone clap your hands.
That's the song you're doing?
Yeah.
I feel like you'll do it better.
Wow, wow, wow.
Freeze.
Everybody, fuck your hand.
We're on our way to the White House.
Lit.
Let's go.
How many times have you been to the White House?
I've been to the White House maybe 20.
We used to play how you go secret room in the White House.
It was me, Barron, and Donnie.
Also in the front lawn, me, Barron, and Donnie would play soccer.
And like everyone would like watch us play soccer going up.
It was really funny.
But yeah, that's a fun fact for you.
Maybe a soccer vlog.
Soccer vlog with me, Barron.
Alright, if you guys want to see that, let me know.
Oh, did we just cut through the White House or no?
We are in the White House.
Look to your right.
Oh, we are in the White House.
Awesome.
Can I get in here?
Awesome, awesome.
Get in here buddy.
Pretty cool.
Yeah, we're in the White House right now.
Alright, and then Emma.
I'm 6'1", what's up with you?
Oh, come on, come on.
Get the tall jeans.
That's great.
Kyle, let's go.
I'm going to be here.
Thank you.
Awesome.
Donnie?
Solo?
Chase, you want to come here?
Professor, check this out.
Do you know each room is a different color?
Yes.
The green room, and then the blue room, and we've got red room.
I like the red room.
Oh, my gosh.
By the way, welcome to the White House.
We're in the White House right now.
Alright,
let's go.
I'm going to see his jacket in real life, I swear.
This is the first one with Captain O'Farr.
Oh, I burned it.
Let's go.
Game time.
They're cheering for me.
I don't know why.
Oh, it's loud out there.
Oh, I'm dancing right now.
I'd rather talk about it.
Honestly, I'd rather sing.
That's what I'd rather sing.
What's about to happen?
Across the stage to be awesome Please welcome the 47th president of the United States
Okay, and first lady of the United States mrs.
Melania Trump USA!
USA!
Welcome Vice President of the United States, J.E.
Vance and second lady, Usha.
Ladies and gentlemen, please welcome members of the Trump family, Don Jr.
and Kai, Ivanka and Jared, Eric and Laura, Tiffany and Michael.
With you, the summer
What
was it like being up there?
I was lost.
Donnie was a horrible dancer, by the way.
That's what I said.
That's why I was like...
Horrible.
Donnie, if you're watching this, buddy, take some dancing lessons.
Like, it was bad.
Like when I go to the rhythm and he starts going faster like it's a
slow the rhythm like slow down How do you think you did?
I think I did like six outside.
I think I did two outside What has it been like 18 hours of walking
today?
Straight?
18 hours of walking in heels That's legit.
Literally I've been up since
And now it's midnight.
Now it's midnight.
We're speeding up the process Marco That
was your one dance right?
No, no, she's got one.
Two dances.
I'm flying on a plane
Cause I'm a superman 3, 2, 1
It's kind
of like a staple on the channel now, you gotta like sing when there's not
a radio Kai you wanna sing it with me?
Snowballs flying on a mountain tonight Snowflakes are turning Seagulls, don't let
them know
And now they know
Let it go, let it go Can't hold it back anymore Cold never bothered
me anyway Alright guys, so we finally made it back to the hotel.
It's like 1am right now.
We went to three balls, danced at two, And so it was just a really
cool day and obviously an experience of a lifetime and very historical and it was
really nice to just like be there with the family today and really enjoy the
moments and also get to film it for you guys as well.
And thank you guys so much for watching.
I'm gonna go to bed.
We gotta leave tomorrow morning and I'm excited for the future so let's just keep
this thing rolling and uh yeah like and subscribe.
Thank you.
Bye bye guys.